COME ON
Come on!
owareru youni
Running like a fugitive,
isoi de iru
being chased by something.
kawai ta mune ga
Inside my heart is pounding,
kari tateru no sa
my throat dry like it's withering.
dare no tame de naku
For no single one,
dare no mono de naku
to none does belong,
ore tachi no ima ga
this time is ours, right now...
itami hodoki kokoro hodoki kage o hodoki
Unraveling the pain, unraveling our hearts, unraveling shadows.
iki o tsunete hashiri nukero yami o saite
Stifling our breath, reaching for beyond, tearing through the dark.
tatakau koto mo aishi au koto mo
In fighting and in love.
owari wa shinai
To the distant light above,
ON THE WAY
yes, we are on the way!
I WANNA ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
I wanna rock... Rockin' my heart...
You're an embarrassment
to our village.
Why do you think we came all
the way here to Leaf Village?
P-Please listen to me, Gaara.
T-They lashed out first...
Shut up!
I'll kill you.
U-Understood, I was wrong.
I-I'm sorry...
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry about that...
This guy... has a nasty look.
To think he was able to hit
that Kankuro
with a tiny rock with great ease.
This guy's... good.
Let's go.
We didn't come here
to play around.
I know.
Hold it!
What is it?
Judging from your headbands,
you're Ninja from the Village
Hidden in the Sand, right?
Without question, the Land of Fire and
the Land of Wind are allied nations.
But the arbitrary coming and
going of Shinobi
is supposed to
be prohibited by the treaty.
State your purpose!
Depending on circumstances...
Hmph! So this is what they mean
by the darkest place being
under the candlestick.
Don't you know anything about it?
My permit!
As you say, we're Sand Village Genin
from the Land of Wind.
We came to this village to
take the Chunin Exam.
Chunin Exam...?
Identify
Yourselves!
The Powerful Enemies
That Have Arrived!!
What is the Chunin Exam anyways?
You really don't know
anything, do you?
Nii-chan, if you pass the exam,
you can become a Chunin from a Genin!
I see! Then, maybe I'll try taking them!
Heh!
Hey! You there...
What's your name?
Huh? M-Me?
No! The gourd next to you!
I'm Gaara of the desert...
I have an interest in you as well...
What's your name?
Uchiha Sasuke.
Say! Say! What about me?
What about me?
Not interested.
Heh! Things have gotten interesting.
Konohamaru, do I look weak?
Compared to Sasuke nii-chan, yes...
Sasuke, I won't lose to you!
What's gotten into you,
all of a sudden?!
What do you think?
I don't think they're anything special.
But the black-haired one from Leaf Village
and the gourd from the Sand Village...
those two need to be checked.
Now then, in conjunction
with beginning the Chunin Exam,
let us first have those in charge
of the rookie Genin come forward.
Kakashi and Kurenai and Asuma...
So? Are there any Genin from
your teams
you wish to recommend
for these exams?
It goes without saying,
but if it's a Genin who has carried out
eight or more formal missions,
you can recommend them
for the exams if you wish.
Well, as a general rule,
having carried out more than twice
that amount of missions is appropriate.
There's no need to hear this...
It's too soon for them.
Then, you first Kakashi.
The Kakashi-led Team 7...
Uchiha Sasuke. Uzumaki Naruto.
Haruno Sakura.
I, Hatake Kakashi, recommend these
three for the Chunin Exam.
Huh?
The Kurenai-led Team 8...
Hyuga Hinata, Inuzuka Kiba,
Aburame Shino.
These three, I, Yuhi Kurenai,
recommend the same.
The Asuma-led Team 10...
Yamanaka Ino, Nara Shikamaru,
Akimichi Choji.
These three, I, Sarutobi Asuma,
recommend the same.
All three recommended...
To think rookies will be
in the Chunin Exam...
Hasn't it been five years
since that's happened?
Hmm...
Wait a minute!
What is it, Iruka?
Hokage-sama, please let me
say one thing.
This may be presumptuous,
but as for the nine names
that were given,
I was in charge of them at the Academy.
Admittedly, they were all students
with ability,
but it's too soon...!
They should be tested after
having gained more experience!
I became a Chunin when I was
six years younger than Naruto is now.
Naruto is different from you!
Is it your intent to crush Naruto?!
They always do nothing but complain
about important missions...
Teaching them a lesson
once would be fun.
Trying to crush them
would be interesting, too.
W-What did you say?!
Well, joking aside...
Iruka-sensei...
I understand what you want to say.
It's aggravating, I know.
However...
Kakashi...
Don't do it.
Stay out of this!
They're not your students anymore!
Now they're my subordinates!
Man... troublesome people.
B-But the Chunin Exam
is also known as...
Iruka...
I understand your point.
Hokage-sama...
Therefore, I have decided to conduct
a special preliminary exam
for these rookie Genin.
P-Preliminary exam...?!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Why is it that he's the one who
always calls us out,
and then makes us wait?!
That's right! That's right!
What's he going to do about
the feelings of a maiden
who accidentally overslept and resigned
herself to no blow-drying?!
I overslept, so I haven't washed my face
and didn't brush my teeth.
Y-You... That's dirty.
Why're these guys so hyper
first thing in the morning?!
Hey, good morning, folks!
Today, I got a bit lost on the path of life...
Right! That's a lie!!
Uh, well...
This is sudden, but I recommended
you guys for the Chunin Exam, so...
Here, these are your applications.
Chunin Exam...
That being said, the recommendations
are not compulsory.
You guys are free to decide whether
you take the Exam or not.
All right! I love you, Kakashi-sensei!
Hey, cut it out. Get away already...
Only those who want to take the Exam,
sign that application and
come to Room 301 of the Academy
at 3:00 p.m. five days from now...
That's it!
Chunin Exam! Chunin Exam!
Chunin Exams, eh...
I bet lots of strong guys would be there...
For example, that guy!
And this guy!
Okay! I won't lose to
anybody no matter what!
If I take the first place, the path to
the Hokage is right there!
Sure enough, it's decided that Naruto
will be the Hokage...
I'll just retire my elderly self at once.
Yay!
I might be able to fight him.
I... don't want to...
Here I can't...
keep up with Sasuke-kun,
and not even with Naruto...
The Chunin Exam, no way...
Oh, Naruto nii-chan! Let's play!
Sure. I don't have any missions today,
so I'll play with you guys!
Yay!
Oh!
Leader! Konohamaru-chan!
What're you going to do with Moegi?!
Hey, you! Let Moegi go!
Damn!
Let's follow them, Konohamaru!
Y-Yeah!
W-Wait!
Chunin Exams, eh...
Yo.
S-Sasuke-kun, what's up?
How about we go for a little walk?
No way! For real?!
Well well... So you can keep up
at this speed, eh?
Wait for me! Moegi!
Nii-chan, where'd you go?
I think we are lost.
No! Let me go!
Even the strongly fortified
Village Hidden in the Leaf...
is mine if I slip in the
middle of Chunin Exam's ruckus.
Hmm?
That was fast...
Hey! You fat old man!
What're you going to do with Moegi?
What am I going to do, you ask?
You want to know?
Wha...?!
Don't move!
If you do,
the brat's dead meat!
Y-You. Why're you doing this?!
I want the first Hokage's
Scroll of Sealing!
If you bring it to me,
I'll return the brat!
Scroll of Sealing...
Umm...
Sasuke-kun...
What's up, all of a sudden?
Sakura...
Give up on the Chunin Exam...
It's too early for you.
Is it...?
I thought so...
The Chunin Exam is
a gathering of top dogs...
You might die if you're not careful...
Sasuke-kun...
So you're worried about me, right?
Yeah... kind of...
What a display of affection, eh?
Get lost! If you don't want to die.
Don't talk as if you know everything!
Don't make me angry!
Sasuke-kun!
Don't take me lightly!
Sasuke-kun?
Sasuke-kun!
Sasuke-kun!!
What're you doing?
Hurry up and bring me
the Scroll of Sealing!
What'll happen... if I say, hell no?
You don't care what happens
to this brat?
Heh, I'm fine with whatever happens
to that bunch of straw.
Wha...?!
When did he do that?!
I've taken Moegi back from you,
thank you!
As expected great leader!
Moegi-san respects you.
Damn it! The Clone Jutsu, huh...?
You don't know when to give up!
Naruto nii-chan!
Hey! You're late, Konohamaru!
Konohamaru-chan, I was scared.
Oh, there-there...
Leader, did you catch him?
Yup, as you can see!
Huh? What?!
Oh, it's the Substitution Jutsu!
Damn it! When did he switch?!
I see...
If you don't want to turn out
like this,
you'll give up on
the Chunin Exam, too.
Sasuke-kun, don't die...!
Big mistake if you think
I'd say that.
I was aware of this Genjutsu
right from the start!
What?!
The real Sasuke-kun wouldn't do
something like
invite me to go for a walk!
Don't make me say
such frustrating things!
That kind of elementary Genjutsu
won't work on me!
Did you say elementary...?
That's right!
Incidentally, I've seen through that
you're also an illusion
and aren't really here!
I don't know about...
that!
See?
Just what I'd expect of
Kakashi's subordinate.
However, this will become reality
in the Chunin Exam!
I wonder if you can endure that...?
I'm not scared!
I'll take them on anytime!
The Chunin Exam isn't...
The Chunin Exam isn't...!
I'm still not sure if I can do it...
That was a stupid thing to do...
How was it?
We went to the trouble of having
a special preliminary exam,
but all nine of the rookies passed.
As you say, it appears their skills
have definitely improved.
Well, the actual Chunin Exam
won't just end at this, but...
Hey, have you heard?
Rookies are going to be
in the Chunin Exam
for the first time in five years.
No way.
It's probably just a Jonin battle of wills
or something anyway.
No...
The story is that three among them
are that Kakashi's unit.
That's interesting...
Well, be that as it may...
That's a sad story...
Sakura-chan, you're late!
Yeah... sorry...
Morning, Sasuke-kun.
Yeah...
Something's strange about Sakura.
So, are you sure you're going
to attempt taking
the Chunin Exam with that skill?
May it'd be best if you runts quit.
You're green-assed brats, after all.
Please let us through.
That's... mean...
What did you say?!
Listen!
We're being nice to you!
The Chunin Exam is a high hurdle.
Many times have we seen
people quit Shinobi
as well as people who were
disabled for life
just because they took this Exam.
Also, a Chunin is at the level
of a unit leader.
Mission failures,
death of subordinates,
it's all part of the
responsibilities of a leader!
A brat such as this a Chunin?
What's so bad about weeding out
those who won't pass anyway?!
A just argument.
However, you will let me through.
And could you also immediately
undo this barrier created with Genjutsu?
I have business on the third floor.
What's this guy talking about...?
I don't know...
— Well, well...
— So you noticed, eh?
How about it, Sakura?
You should've been
the first one to realize it.
Huh...?
Your analytical strength and
Genjutsu know-how
has improved the most in our squad, so...
Sasuke-kun...
Thank you...
Of course. I realized it ages ago!
You see, this is the second floor!
Yup!
Well, not bad...
But all you've done is to catch on.
Right?!
H-He's fast!
This person...
He's a different person from
when he was getting punched before!
He stopped my kick...
What's with that Chakra in his arm?
Hey, this isn't what you promised.
You were the one who said
you didn't want to carelessly
attract attention and be watched.
But...
Oh boy...
This again...
This guy...
The marks where he was hit
are disappearing.
Was he faking?
My name's Rock Lee.
Your name's Sakura-san, right...?
Huh?
Please go out with me!
I'll protect you until I die!
Absolutely... not.
Huh?
You're... too intense.
Hey, you there.
Identify yourself.
Damn it! Again?
It's always about Sasuke!
When asking someone his name,
give your own name first.
You're... a rookie, right?
How old are you?
I'm not obliged to answer.
What...?
Cute.
Too intense, huh...
Uninterested, huh...
Now then!
Sasuke-kun, Naruto, let's go!
So those are Kakashi and
Guy's treasured brats.
Well, for the time being,
their applications will pass.
Yeah...
It appears this year's test-takers
will be amusing...
For us proctors too, eh.
Good grief...
This Chunin Exam...
is full of monsters.
Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
Break into the contents, never falling down.
My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve.
Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting for people like me.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry...
Bowl-cut, fuzzy eyelashes
and bushy eyebrows.
Oh! It's you!
You're the overly intense guy
who just got rejected by Sakura-chan.
What's with your bizarre
green jumpsuit?
What? You want to challenge me,
bushy-browed bumpkin?
I'll teach you that it's a million years
too soon to be doing that.
Next episode:
"Energy 120%. A Modern and Rocking Challenge!"
As for me,
I'm going to kick butt once again!